Bowers, Mollie H. Police and Firefighter Arbitration 5568
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mollie H. Bowers Police and Firefighter Arbitration
1965-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Bowers, Mollie H.
5568
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Files of the arbitrator Mollie H. Bowers, including documentation of police and firefighter arbitrations in Michigan, Pennsylvania, Oregon, Wisconsin, and New York City.
5664272
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 03, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 18, 2019
Scope and Contents
Files of the arbitrator Mollie H. Bowers, including documentation of police and firefighter arbitrations in Michigan, Pennsylvania, Oregon, Wisconsin, and New York City.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5456: Mollie H. Bowers Collection of Arbitration and Fact Finding Decisions Regarding Police and Fire Fighters
Arbitration, Industrial; Police -- Labor unions -- United States; Collective bargaining -- Police -- United States; Fire fighters -- Labor unions -- United States; Collective bargaining -- Fire fighters -- United States; Bowers, Mollie H.
5664272
- Arbitration; Police, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Arbitration; Firefighters, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Arbitration, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Arbitration Officers + Firefighters, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Arbitration; Officers + Firefighters, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Mollie H. Bowers, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Fraternal Order of Police, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Installment 3 Michigan, 1965-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Pennsylvania Installment 2, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Installment 2 Michigan, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Installment 2 Michigan, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Installment 3 Michigan (a bit of Pa too See tales), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Arbitration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Mollie H. Bowers; To Richard Strasberg, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)